Uh...?
Who is it? At first.
Who was it?
Are you seeing him later tonight?
Would you go out with me if you wanted to?
Go ahead, say it.
I've always wanted to talk to Dan-El.
After the rain, we're still having a little chat.
Ready?
Even when it's raining, it's still raining
Let's have a rain chat for short!
Hello to all of you who are watching our official YouTube Live Ameflash channel. We are AmeFlash.
We are AmeFlash, and we look forward to working with you. Yuzu did the title call this time.
Yes, we are Yuzu.
I knew we could chat normally with one more small group. Oh, there was no
He commented. There were two of us last time. The week before last. I am sorry. I have been absent.
I couldn't keep up the conversation. You were having a great time, weren't you?
I was also absent, so I had to drop some episodes about Kojima-san and so on.
If you are going to take a break, take a proper break.
I don't want you to do anything unnecessary.
You don't have to work at all. I don't need to work at all.
You don't need that kind of work, do you?
I don't need that kind of work?
I'll be careful from now on.
I'll take a break when I have to.
Yes, thank you very much, Mr. Dodara.
Thank you very much.
May I read the script? Mr. Ichikawa.
For the title call, the part about how you've always wanted to talk to us,
We will choose one person from those who tweeted their impressions of Ameshabe and call that person's name.
Please tweet your thoughts on the program with the hashtag Ameshabe. Please do so.
So, this is the first Ameshabe in two weeks.
It's been a while since we've all been together. It's been a while.
It's been three weeks?
Yeah, about 3 weeks. About?
Like three weeks.
I was in Taiwan last week, so I couldn't make it,
Not this year. I can do it this week.Not this year. I can do it this week.
That's right.
Let's talk a lot.
Now, so there are many appearances during this time, such as Taiwan Gyosei and Tiff,
I have a lot of things I want to talk about. Everyone.
That's right.
By the way, what about this time?
You got it? Tweet.
Not yet.
Not yet?
I'm sorry.
Just now,
Yes, I'm sorry.
Aira was on Idol Ramen Collection just now, wasn't she?
That's right. I was performing.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
How is it?
I was able to perform at Girl Dawwad for the first time last time,
I think I have made ramen noodles based on the advice I received there,
I was really nervous, but it was fun.
I was really nervous, but it was fun,
That's the only thing I envy.
The catering was delicious,
It was like a summer vegetable curry.
It was really delicious,
And for dinner, there were onigiri (rice balls), fried rice balls, and so on,
Spaghetti with hamburger steak, and so on,
There were delicious dishes like rice balls, fried rice balls, hamburgers, spaghetti, and so on,
I'm jealous.
I was so happy.
I love it. I wish I could have been there.
It's not that I wanted to go, it's more like I wanted to go.
I want to be a regular member of Amehei.
I'm very happy to be invited as an individual,
It's good for me to be invited as an individual, and it's also good for me to learn.
I thought again that it would be nice to perform at Ame Taira.I thought again that it would be nice to get out in the rain flat.
But the three of us were watching it together too.
I watched it on TikTok live.
I wanted to go see it,
I couldn't go because I had a lesson at work,
So we all watched it together on the stream,
You were super cute.
Thank you so much.
Hana told me that the three of us went out for dinner,
I thought Ayala will definitely break up with them.
Isn't that dangerous?
The three of us went out for dinner,
Okay, bye-bye. See you later.
I thought it would be better to break up.
I'm kidding,
How many times have you guys broken up?
But I heard that the three of us watched together,
Ayala was the cutest,
They even saw me in my second term,
They said they would never break up again.
Never again.
That's heavy.
Love is heavy.
They watch over me like this every time,
I'm very happy for the members.
Thank you.
No, I'm not.
You didn't see me that excited, did you?
It was really pretty exciting, wasn't it?
I was transferring the moment Ayala came out.
I was at home looking at my phone while I was changing,
I was at home, changing planes, looking at my cell phone, when I saw the comment "Ayala",
You were in the middle of a discussion?
The signal was bad, so I lost my signal.
I saw ayara's comment on both of you,
It's probably there! Look, quick!
Signal! Radio wave! I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.I'm so happy.
It was stairs, but there weren't too many people,
I didn't stop for a moment.
I just stopped and looked.
You didn't know exactly what time we were leaving.
It was about the time, right?
That was the first one.
Imagine, I'm sure it's going to be here,
Move along,
We're all on the same team, so why don't we just ask them?
Sure.
I don't know what time he'll be out.
You can't abuse your discretion like that.
To us.
Where are you being humble.
But thank you very much.
You all came to the site, too, and also through the distribution,
I was very happy to receive DMs and messages from those who came to the event.
There were even people who called out our names and shouted at us,
It was very encouraging.
I wish I could have come.
Thank you very much.
But thank you so much,
Madoka Saito?
Madoka Saito, the tea no-man, came to see Ayara and said she was a fan,
She came to see Ayala and said she was a fan,
When I passed by her, I thought she was cute,
I thought she was cute,
I was just passing by her and said, "Good job.
It was right before the show,
I was fixing my bangs on my cell phone.
And then, you know,
I'm a fan. He asked me to take his picture,
I was so happy.
He saw the Metamorphose music video and fell in love with me.
So you're Nozomi, right?
That's Mr. Nozomako.
He told me he had been supporting me for a long time,He told me he's been supporting me for a long time,
I'm glad.
I was happy because I didn't expect it to happen.
Did you have a chance to talk to anyone?
Yes, I did.
But, you know, with Honoka,
Yes, yes. Honoka was at the show, too,
I wanted to say hello,
The president of the company.
Yes, I took a TikTok with Honoka, the president of the company.
I took a TikTok with Honoka, the president of the company.
Oh! Nice!
I think it will probably go up now,
Drama and Tan Twister.
You filmed both?
Yes, I did. Tan Twister was a guerrilla act,
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to seeing the cute Honoka,
Please look forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it. Well, that's the end of Ayanan's story.
I'm afraid that if I talk too much, I'll come off as a spoiled brat,
I don't know why.
I think it's better to end with just saying, "She's beautiful.
I want to ask you something more,
I want to ask you something more, like, "Was she cute?
You didn't talk to anyone, did you? To be honest.
Like, "Fruit Zipper was cute.
To be honest, you haven't talked to anyone, have you?
What?
Maybe you're just pretending not to hear me.
Why?
Ayanan can't talk.
Why not?
Okay? Let's just end it here.
Why?
You were cute, Fruit Zipper.Fruit Zipper, you were so cute.
Was she cute? The end.
Okay.
I think I'm done then.
Suddenly, there was a girl, too.
And we could talk.
Hmm? I didn't even get to talk to Ikinari-chan, so I'm screwed.
The backstage was far away, wasn't it?
Backstage, you know, it looks like it faces the wall.
I can choose.
Who were you backstage with?
Honoka was with me for that kind of thing,
I was with all the girls in the TikTok section.
Oh, that's right.
It's not good to be facing the wall when Honoka is there.
I sat in the furthest corner.
I didn't know Honoka was there.
So that's how it is.
Yes, that's right.
You said something about curry for lunch,
But I told her that I was going to eat a little more vegetables because I would be too hungry, so she gave me her lunch box,
But she ate the curry more beautifully.
But she ate the curry.
Why is that?
I told her that she should eat more vegetables, so I told her to focus on the vegetables,
But the curry was so much better than I expected that I ate more of the curry.
I thought about whether I should fill my stomach with curry or vegetables, and I preferred curry.
Please go ahead with the spacha spacha.
Okay? Go ahead.
Okay, first, a little bit of spacha spacha.
Okay.
Toi-san.
Thank you for your hard work as a Shinobi. It was fun.
Ilan was wonderful today.
Thank you very much.
Oh no, he's gone.
I'm sorry, my speech was too long.
Oh, there it is.Ah, there it is.
Yukatamu-san.
Thank you for your hard work on the idol runway, Ilan.
I couldn't be there, but I was able to watch the streaming video, and she shined the brightest.
I hope we can all perform together next time.
Thank you very much.
Next, Ms. Kakutei. A miracle happened, so I'd like to report it.
I was supposed to go on a trip to Disney from the 12th, but I cut a day off and went to Roppongi,
I was planning to take a trip to Disney on the 12th, but I was able to cut one day off my Disney vacation to go to the Amehura Live in Roppongi.
I'm taking Smileage with me.
What!
Cutting out Disney?
Isn't that great?
Let's make it fun.
Let's make it a dreamland.
I'm so excited.
Dreamland.
Electrical parade.
Tentereten-ten.
Elektric parade.
Looking forward to it. Thank you very much.
Next, Naoto from Osaka.
My first overseas expedition was great.
It was many times more fun than I expected. Thank you for Amefura.
Thank you very much.
A lot of people are coming.
YTXZ I got a spacha from Mr. Kimchi of Shippo.
Thank you very much.
Next, Toa-san.
Ira, thanks for the idle run. I watched you on the feed and you were really cool.
I could see a different kind of coolness from the usual live performance,
Ira is stoic, so I wonder if he worked hard on muscle training and diet for this day?
I thought the runway was the best show for Ira.
Thank you very much.
Next, Nao-san.
I had too much fun in Taiwan, so I'm looking forward to the look back talk.
Thank you very much.
Is that all?Is that all?
Mr. Taiga.
From Taiga-san to everyone at Amefla, thank you for your hard work on TIFT Taiwan.
I found Ayla on TikTok a while ago, and then I found Amefura and fell in love with them both.
I'm 19 years old and I'm a carpenter and I'm having a hard time at work,
I am 19 years old and I am a carpenter and when I am having a hard time at work, Amefura's music always cheers me up.
I am thinking of joining the fan club.
If I join, I will go to various live shows and try my best to be recognized by the members.
Lastly, I am very sorry, but I would like to keep working hard,
I would appreciate it if you could send me a message of support.
Yes, sorry.
I know you have a really hard job even though you are 19 years old,
I'm sure you must be going through a lot of hardships,
I'm sure you're going through a lot of hard times, but we at Amefurracy will be there to cheer you on,
Please keep in touch with us here at Ameflacy.
Good luck!
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
I'm rooting for you!
That's great.
You're too good.
Osawa-chan, next you will be a carpenter.
I think it's really hard work being a carpenter.
It's amazing.
Well, there are so many more things I want to talk about.
First, the Taiwanese satellite, and then Gifu,
There are so many things I want to talk about,
So I would like to start this week with this corner.
So, President Moemiwa, please begin.
Yo! Puddle!
[Applause]
Thank you very much.
They are clapping so much.
By the way, we were absent from the teacher's room for quite a while, so I just want to know what you mean.
Does it mean we can't ride?
It means we didn't see it.It means you haven't seen it.
Why not! I was clapping. I got in.
That means you didn't see it.
Moehana, the two of you? Even though you two were working hard for the rest of the night?
When Isla drooped, Hana was really upset.
It was scary.
That was the only part I saw.
I saw Yuzuki at the beginning.
I watched it while I was sick, and I thought it was a bad idea to watch it when I was sick, so I watched it right away.
I'll watch it after I get better.
I'll see it after I get well.
After that, I saw it.
After 5 minutes, I got sick.
I decided not to watch it.
That's an excuse.
We've already been to so many festivals.
I'm grateful for that.
So, I hope you will do the same.
If you think you can do samadhi, please do.
If I think I can do samadhi, I will do it.
I see.
Samadai.
Somehow it's a reflection.
Tentouko eirei.
Yes, yes, yes.
By all means.
The two of you who have been resting, I hope you will be able to put in a lot of work.
I'd like you to set an example.
We are in festival mode right now.
By cutting the older members out, we can watch their backs and fall in love with their cheques.
Momokuro-san is leading the idol world in March,
We don't know what it would be like without such a person.
If the top of the idol world is Momo Kuro,
I want you to be the top of the sushi sammai world.
What are you talking about?
The top of the sushi world is the president of Sushimanmai.The top of the sushi sampler is the president of Sushi Sampler.
No doubt.
Definitely.
Then what are today's abeshabu and president Kojima and samadhi so far?
Yes.
If you don't shut up, you're out.
Out, right? As it is now.
Well, but, you know, like this.
You guys can't say anymore.
Don't appeal to the camera.
I'm not talking.
I was going to ask you if you did.
You're not talking at all.
You two are a little unfocused today.
Oh, no?
Just because we're idols doesn't mean
Just because you're an idol doesn't mean you can't leave a 5-second gap.
Not during the show, not during the show.
You have to answer within 3 seconds.
No, no, no. I'm done.
I just want to say thank you.
Who cares?
I want to post it on my Instagram.
But it's never done.
Please hang in there. I'll finish in five minutes.
So, can I tell you our story before the disconnect?
Yes, please.
First of all, we did the time line, right?
Yes! Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I was so happy to see so many people come to the fan tour.
Yes, there was a good turnout.
But I didn't think Amefurashi and Kinako-san would get together like that, so I was really happy.
It was the second time for us to go to Taiwan, since we had to shoot a music video there.
So I was really worried if all the fans would come,
How many were there?
About 30? No, a little more.
No, a little more. Wait, four people per table.Wait, four people per table.
If there were 7 people,
But that's about 30 people.
But isn't that great? You brought 30 people to Taiwan.
That's great.
If there were 10 people, I think it would be great.
Really.
How many of us came this time, too?
31 people.
31?
That's great.
What do you mean, five days and four nights?
Five days, yes, five days and four nights.
I spent 4 nights and 5 days,
Not 6 days and 5 nights?
I dare you to say 6 days and 5 nights?
Oh, I see. Since we had a client.
We had a very long stay.
That's right.
First, we had two days of live performances, and then we were able to do some sightseeing afterwards. This time.
Yes, we had time for sightseeing this time.
We didn't have time for sightseeing when we did the music video, but this time we were able to enjoy Taiwan to the fullest.
It was fun. 10 minutes, 9 minutes, night markets, Harajuku.
Ximending.
Yes, that's it.
Like Harajuku.
It was quite a hard schedule for you to visit all of them in one day, wasn't it? Sightseeing.
But it was fun.
We got to see a lot of places in a short time, so let's talk about the live show.
I don't need to talk about the live show.
You don't have to talk about the live show.
The live show went off with a bang as usual.
It was great. The audience said Taiwan was delicious. Taiwan was delicious.
You must think I'm talking about food.
It's true.
But first of all, you went there by plane.
Yes, we did.
Did anything happen here? We are going to look back from the first day like this.Did anything happen here? This is how we look back from the first day.
Every time. One more time.
I have a complaint.
Is your voice cut off?
Yes, it is.
Oh! It's off!
It's off!
What is it?
We are made of food.
Life is made of food.
Whenever you board an airplane, there is a certain area.
I'm either in the front or the back of the plane. Usually, I'm always in the front or the back.
It's usually the seats.
In the end, the seats are divided into three sections.
So I'm either in the front or in the back.
Oh! I say, "You're the first one to eat in-flight.
I'm so happy.
But then, the meal comes from the other side. The meal comes from the other side.
And we ended up being the last.
There are definitely two kinds of food, but since we were the last, there was only one kind, so we couldn't choose. There is no choice.
Fish.
You can choose beef or fish, but it's always fish.
I like fish. But you want meat, right?
You've always had fish. In-flight meals.
I like meat.
I like meat, too.
Because the only time we could eat meat was in Thailand.
Everything else was fish.
Fish is good, too.
And it was on the way back, too. It was pasta & beef on the way back.
Oh, Japanese food. Japanese food.
Pasta is Japanese food.
I have some pasta left.
It's delicious. It's delicious after all, but you want to choose, don't you? I thought, "I'll have two.
I thought, "I'll come back again," but on the way back, it was the other way around too.
When the CA came in front of me, I was talking to the customer in front of me,
When the CA came in front of me and was talking to the passenger in front of me, her expression was wrinkled between her eyebrows.
That was never there.That one is definitely not there.
I apologize for only having one right now.
Absolutely ONLY.
And then, sure enough, he told me there was only one, and I could read his expression.
So, I was thinking, I want to pick the next row student.
I wanted them to come from us.
Malaysia is a 7-hour flight.
We want to be rewarded, don't we? I'm sure you're right.
What was that all about?
It's really quite frequent.
That's it? That's it?
That's what I'm talking about.
This is...
That's...
That's it, right?
That's the one before, right?
That's it?
That's the one?
Oh, senpai.
Alone in the dark...
Isolation.
What is samadhi samadhi?
Isolation?
Can I just have a candy bar? Like that.
No, just candy-floss every time.
That's true.
It's like bullying.
That's right.
But Shien-san is always so nice to me.
They're so polite, and they bring us delicious food.
You know, they don't always carry us around on bad footing.
They don't carry a lot of things on bad footing.
I don't use it much.
It's shaking!
It shakes!
It's too narrow, and it doesn't have a pull.
That's why I can forgive them. They're always so nice.So I can forgive you. You're always so nice to me.
You're right.
And this time we had Häagen-Dazs.
Yes, this time we had Haagen-Dazs. So it's a zero balance.
It's good. It's good after all.
Our desire to choose.
We want to choose.
It's nice to have an environment where you can say, "Which one is better?
It's not like, "This is it.
We want to choose, yes.
I want to be able to choose.
It was really good. I especially liked it on the way home.
It was delicious.
There was soba on the side, too.
The soba was delicious.
And the absolute best part of every meal is the bread!
Bread!
The bread is so good!
This round bread!
Delicious butter too!
It's a unique bread for airplanes!
I wonder where they make that?
Delicious!
I want two in the plane!
It's got a nice, buttery crust.
I want to take that home with me!
This time, there are so many movies to watch.
We'll talk about airplanes again.
There were a lot of movies.
And Yazu saw two of them.
And the second one I only got halfway through, so
So, on the way home, we watched the rest of the movie.
It's an animated movie called "Gotoh's Bride".
I was watching it, so I started halfway through.
So I started from the halfway point, and then I saw the first half hour.
Like, it's going to be over in about an hour.
And just then the in-flight meal came.
And Yuzu was crying so hard right then.So, Yuzu, it was when you were crying really hard right now.
And while I was crying a lot, I kept hearing things like "fushan pon" being asked around and around.
I was thinking, "Not now.
I didn't even notice that Yuzu was crying next to me.
And that's bad, you know, everybody, my dinner was coming after I cried.
So everyone was looking in my direction.
I wondered why they didn't see me crying.
I thought back to everyone's face very carefully.
They were all looking only at that CA's face.
Not Yuzu.
They were looking at the CA's face diagonally in front of me.
What's more important than the yuzu's face is the food on the plane.
They were looking this way, but...
They were looking at me, not at her.
Not the yuzu.
He was crying so hard he was sniffing his nose or something.
I had no idea.
I didn't recognize her at all.
I was like, "You don't have that look on your face.
Even though it made us all depressed.
I kept looking down.
I didn't notice Yuzu crying at all.
I was sad too.
I was sad. I was sad.
I was so sad.
I thought it was rare that Yuzu didn't talk to me.
That's what happened.
Yuzu watches a lot of movies, right?
You watch a lot of movies.
And he cries.
He doesn't watch them at all.
They're so silly.
Like on the plane.
I think it's a Conan movie.
The Conan movie.
That's right, the Conan movie.
I'm reading the blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah.
When you touch the screen, there's a lot of explanatory text.When you touch something, there's a lot of description.
of the movie.
And it's very long and mysterious.
I read it all the way to the end.
You don't have to read it.
You don't have to read it, do you?
That's why these two are so bad.
I really don't want to go on a private trip with them.
But they're mysteriously putting us next to each other.
They sit next to each other a lot.
It's so much fun.
Maybe we should talk.
So, Yuzu.
Aira did all the work on the inside.
I'm glad she did.
I liked it outside.
It's just like the two of you.
When they get together...
I'm sure they'll do something.
Do something funny.
You haven't dumped me recently.
I have.
I'm exploring with Morila and Hana.
She just doesn't do it when I shake her.
I see. I see.
There's less shaking, right?
Yeah, it's gone down, really down.
That's why I go outside every time.
I don't really get involved with those two.
But Yuzu was messing with you too, right?
He kept trying to get her to watch the movie.
I only gave him a ride because Hana was doing it.
Aira's in a movie.
It's crazy.
They were having so much fun.
Aiara? I'm pretty sure it was Hana.
And yet... the two of them...And yet... we both are.
If there's a screen here...
You and me together, like this.
Like this.
We talked to each other.
It's really gone.
You guys are gone.
You're scary, you youngest.
It was fun.
You know how hard it is to get on a plane every time.
Why don't you take the boat?
Next time, no one's going to talk.
It's going to be like that.
There are more flights.
Let's just go.
Let's go next.
We've arrived in Taiwan.
Two gigs, two days...
And that's it.
Sightseeing
Sightseeing!
I want to talk about the concert.
The night of the show, right?
Yes, the night of the concert.
Didn't you go somewhere else at night?
That was the night of the show.
Fan meeting, right?
Dinner.
That was the first day, right?
Not a one-day potluck.
The second day is the night.
Yes, the second day is a day potluck.
And it's not.
Let's talk about the second day before we go to Sunnabe.
I told him about the fan meeting.
Right.
Just in case.
Just a little bit.Hey, hey, hey.
Someone came all the way to Taiwan.
Let's talk about it.
We performed on both the first and second days.
We had a fan meeting on the night of the first day.
We all had dinner together.
That's right.
It was so much fun!
We had a karaoke contest.
We sang all the songs and had everyone call out to us.
We sang and danced to the songs
and we sang and danced to the songs that people requested.
I don't remember what song we sang.
Well, we finally did it!
We performed Shonanokaze's "Suirenko" in front of everyone.
That's right.
We had a competition in the backstage forest.
It was the first time to perform in front of everyone.
I only showed as much as I could, but...
It's still our mouth, isn't it?
Totkko Hamster
Yuzu's solo
Hamutaro
hamster
Totoko Hamster
It's a normal animal.
Hamster
It's so funny.
Totoko Hamutaro.
Yuzu solo.
That's right.
Yuzu's first solo.
Not the first.
My way bijs.
It's definitely going to happen.
If we were to do it together...
Everyone said they couldn't sing.Everyone says I can't sing.
I can definitely sing.
I've heard it. I know it.
I just don't know it
Here we go, all at once, the seventh round
Seeds of the air
Me too
So instead of not being able to sing
I got to be in the chorus group
I've been doing it for a long time, just like Har
Ha!
And then we came out.
You sang a lot of songs.
Yes, we did.
Moemi...
No.
Yuzu sang a solo.
The rest of us sang together.
Yuzu sang that song alone.
But with Yuzu.
Yes, Hanae Ran
I sang Hanamizuki
And I'm sorry it was so cute with Yuzu and Moomi
We all sang together, but
Yuzu and Moomi sang together for the most part.
I see
Hanamizutsugetsu (Flower and Water Moon)
You really can't see it, can you?
If you come to the fan tour...
If you don't have it, you can't see it.
That's not true.
It's never like that.
It's like a party with everyone.
I see.
And Kinako is so...
She's got a great sense of humor.
About Amefura...I've heard so much about Amefura.
Like it's funny.
He told me that he really liked me.
He joined in on the water duet.
We got so excited together.
It's not that easy to find.
That's right.
People don't often join in.
They often don't join in.
Kinako's amazing.
She joined us.
She got into the groove.
And then it was Kinako's turn.
many times.
Two songs.
Yes, Kinako sang.
Kinako sang.
and we were the back dancers.
without permission.
Yes, I did.
We're good at backup dancers.
Can I be a back-up dancer?
I said...
Is that okay? Like...
Like, "Sure, we'd be really happy to.
If it's okay with us.
Backup dancers.
You'll never see that.
There are times we've done that.
Back-up dancers.
I've been a back-up dancer for many years.
I'm a professional.
I'm a professional back-up dancer.
That's right.
Kinako is so kind.
She was really kind.
I've seen her on TikTok.
I've seen her on TikTok, but I've always had an image of her as a cool person.I had an image of him being cool, but he's not like that at all.
But it's totally different.
He said it's really nice.
I'm so glad she said that.
I was so happy that he had it.
Moeka and I got involved with each other.
Yuzu and Airako...
It was the first time I'd had a chance to talk to them.
I was pretty nervous at first.
But they were so chatty and got along so well with each other.
That's right.
They were adults.
At first, I thought...
Moechi is the closest to you.
So you took the lead...
You told me.
Yes, yes...
No, no...
No...
No. No.
I just wanted to bother you.
It's okay, it's okay.
You're shaking your head, too, Mr. Yuchiwawa.
I'm shaking my head all the time.
That's what I'm doing.
It's amazing.
Like this.
It's so nice to meet you.
I've been told...
I have a habit of doing that.
I'm sorry.
Next time I see you, it'll be for the first time.
That's not good.
I'm resetting.
Reset girls.
That's what I really mean.
I'll be reset.
If you want, Yuzu could have talked more.If you want, Yuzu might have talked more.
I don't remember that.
With Kinako.
No, I couldn't.
But you know, like the second day of the fan tour.
Our music video.
Blow Your Mind, and we did the switch tour and stuff.
We all did it together.
With all those fans.
With everyone?
We went around with the fans.
We were so close.
You don't usually get to walk that close to people.
You don't get to walk around the city like that.
Walking the streets with the audience at such a distance.
And we're standing next to them.
I don't think that's necessary.
The last one...
When I say it's hot, they all look up.
It's cooler.
That's nice.
Terrible fan tour.
It's fun to be a fan.
It's an experience you don't get to have.
The flowers and the fans were so happy.
It was so great to see everyone there.
They were so happy to see us.
Thank you for coming such a long way to be with us.
Thank you so much.
I'd like to share with you my reflections on the first day of the event.
I'd like to thank you all for coming with us from such a long way away.
We had a strategy meeting in the time between fan meetings.
We wrote the setlist in a flash.
Day 2?
You wrote all the songs.
It was a manga expo.
Japanese anime was very popular.Japanese animation was very popular.
That's why idols
Everyone was fascinated by them.
And they put that song in there.
The buzz was so great that everyone danced to the song first.
And then pull the song out for everyone.
We wrote a setlist with a lot of thought.
The second day was a great success.
It was a lot of fun.
I know you had some fans there.
They said, "Thank you so much for coming to Ame-Flashie.
It was so nice to welcome you.
It's like we're connected.
I'm so grateful for that.
But...
The second day of the show was over.
It's been 10 hours.
After the fan muse work was over
After we said goodbye to everyone.
What did we do?
Day 1?
Day 2.
First, we went to buy tapioca and stuff.
Tapioca, green onion buns...
We went to buy tapioca and green onion buns.
The green onion buns were the first day.
Negipan is the first day.
That's day one.
We went to drink tapioca.
I went for a tapioca drink.
And I had some beef.
Beef drink!
I was told in advance that I was going to go to Nichiname.
but I thought
I thought it would be too spicy
I thought, "What if it's really spicy?
What if I can't eat it?So I thought, what if I can't eat it?
I don't know if I can eat it all.
I don't know if it's good for my palate.
If it's too spicy, I can't eat it.
So I thought, "Well, I don't know.
So I decided to put something in my stomach.
So I put a little something in my stomach
I can eat a little.
Even if I can't eat, I'm still very hungry.
I decided to put a little bit of food in my stomach, so that even if I can't eat it
When we went to Taiwan to shoot a music video
When we went to Taiwan to shoot a music video, we only ate the yuzu and it was delicious.
I taught everyone when to eat tapioca.
And also to watch Starbucks Ilan.
And also
When we were all going around to the music video
I had a chance to visit
I got some beef noodle from a guy at the restaurant
He gave me a bowl of rice vermicelli.
You remember me?
We were walking in the crosswalk.
I was walking a long way.
He welcomed us from a long way away.
We all hugged.
I was so surprised.
He was so sweet and remembered me.
He said bye bye bye, he was so cute.
Eat up, eat up, eat up!
I was so happy.
I thought you'd forgotten about me.
Please buy me some rice vermicelli.
Beef noodle soup.
I said I don't want it.
It was so good!
It was really...
It was warm.
Couldn't you get a little more?Wasn't there a little more to it?
And Ira and...
The time before the potluck...
Yuzu and Ira.
Hana and Mojimi first.
And Ira and Yuzu...
I went there with my friends before.
I recommended a souvenir shop
It's close by.
I told Ira about it.
We went there and bought a ton of stuff.
They give you all the staples.
Oh, my God.
Eat your staples.
It's so good.
We can't stop.
They'll say, "This one's on my mind, too.
Oh, my God.
Boom.
We can't stop.
Hey, mom.
This one's good, too.
I can't stop.
It's delicious.
I took it to the hotel and we ate it.
It's a souvenir.
I was pretty full.
I was about 11 minutes into my meal when I went to the hotpot.
How about you two?
We bought some clothes.
Hannah...
She said she saw a cute clothing store.
So I said, "Let's go there.
I found this one that I wanted.
I tried it on.
I looked at the price.
I looked up the price in Japanese yen.I looked up how much it costs in Japanese yen.
20,000.
That's expensive! I thought.
I said I can't do it.
I'll give it back.
I'm not going to do it.
After that...
I was wondering if you had any good souvenirs.
I'm sure I can find something only in Taiwan.
I found a nice store.
We went shopping there.
And then...
She checked the price for me.
My price was so wrong.
The price was absolutely ridiculous.
The price was like...
For one hand cream...
7,000 yen.
I thought, "That's definitely not right.
I thought, "Maybe this is a mistake.
So I looked it up.
from a totally different country.
from a completely different country.
I'm worried.
That's why we wanted what we wanted.
I thought maybe the clothes we wanted were totally different.
I looked it up, and it's totally different.
So we went back to the store.
We went back and bought it.
It was so cute.
I wanted one too.
I found it and thought it was cute.
I looked at Hannah and said, "Isn't this cute?
I told her it was cute.
She bought a different color.
Please listen to me.Listen to me.
Why are you mad at me?
I'm going sightseeing.
You said you let me do some sightseeing on the last day.
Or four days in one day.
On the last day.
There was a cute clothing store.
I bought the same bag there.
I found that too.
Let Hannah tell you.
It's so cute!
She has a lot of matching burgundies.
Because Hannah did it.
You want her to pick one, right?
No, that's not it.
I'm the one who found the store in the first place.
Hana found it.
I told her about it.
Hana was picking out some pants.
She said they were cute.
The ones she wanted, too.
I had gone to look at them by myself first.
I thought they were cute.
She said she'd try them on.
Then Hana said she'd try it on too.
So we ended up together.
So we bought two of the same one in Taiwan.
I bought two identical ones in Taiwan.
Actually, we have the same lipstick in Thailand.
It's a mystery.
We have so many matching lipsticks.
We're good friends.
They're good friends.
Mr. Osawa doesn't seem happy about it.
He absolutely hates it.
He doesn't want to match.
I want to have something matching with everyone.
It's this mindset.It's this mindset.
Like it's okay if we match.
"I want them to match.
Yuzu and Hana didn't make them matching either.
It's just that they're together.
You know, carbon pants.
I want something like that too.
I want to go shopping with you.
I'm a little scared now, and I'm going off on a tangent.
Yuzu Taiwan's music video
When we were shooting the music video
Hannah was having trouble finding clothes.
She said she wanted pants and shorts.
Yuzu gave her some recommendations
Yuzu told Hana about a store he recommended.
Hana and I went to the store on our way home from Lilybees
Yuzu and Hana happened to be together.
Yuzu and Hana happened to want the same thing.
I bought it and Ayla wanted it so much
I got on line with them on Kocha.
like, "Where's that brand?
I want one too.
You're gonna get one, Ira.
I don't want to add to your collection.
We just happen to match.
I really don't want to.
It's just that it's so cute.
I thought you'd buy one too.
Moei said the other day...
I want to go there, too.
Wait, what if there are four of us?
I know you don't like it.
I know you don't want to.
We don't have to wear the same thing.
I asked Hana about it.
Actually, I asked her about the brand.
Hannah doesn't know.I don't know about Hannah.
So I asked Yuzu.
That's when I asked Hana.
Maybe Yuzu would know if I asked him about the newest thing.
She asked me why.
I thought maybe she didn't like it.
I bought a different one.
I bought a different brand.
I don't like it at all.
Don't worry.
I'm sure you'll buy it.
It's like they can see right through you.
Just because I want to buy it.
I didn't want to tell you.
You know that blue Yuzu set-up?
It's the same brand.
She's gonna buy it.
Yuzu's cute.
I don't know what brand it is.
I don't know.
I always buy from the same place.
If I ask why...
I just say I think it's cute.
What was that?
Nothing.
Like, it doesn't mean anything.
What's that?
Just say you think he's cute.
I don't feel bad.
It's like you can see right through me.
I really didn't like it.
You can see right through me.
That's why you think I'm an easy girl.
I'm an easy girl.
I was so stubborn.
Then go put them on.
I'll wear them with Yuzu sometime.
The ones I bought.The one I bought.
Yuzu and etc.?
the other day, and the American Chave
Pants and Crocs...
We happened to have matching ones.
I was wearing both of them.
Their matching Crocs are also
They're so cute!
Hana and I wore the same pair of Crocs.
My friend works at the store.
We decided to get matching Crocs.
If you're going to go to the store and buy them together
As it is.
Let's go.
I'll be there.
Please look forward to it.
I want to buy matching outfits for the four of us. Taiwan. I want to. I bought a dress in Thailand.
I bought a dress in Thailand, but now that I think about it... it's only in Thailand that I can wear it. If it were in Japan, it'd be buried in the back of my closet.
I want to buy something in Malaysia. I love Malaysia.
Ira was talking about how he wanted to buy I LOVE TAIWAN, and we already had a cute one, so that's fine.
I'll never wear it, so I don't need it. What? I love Taiwan. But they weren't that into it either.
Yuzu said it's fine, as long as everyone buys one
I feel the same way I don't want it, but... if everyone buys the flowers...
You're a realist. I'm a realist. No, no, really... maybe it's just my low voice, but...
Well, I don't really have that much use for it, so... it's nice to think that people will wear it on the way home, right?
It's quite rare to get a card on the way home.
I'll read it... and I'm waiting for the water lily cover for the Japan standby group... and I thought Ayla's skirt fashion that day was very unusual.
I thought Ayla's skirt was very unusual that day.
And I thought, "I don't want to do Rashida.
I thought it was the other way around. Yes, it's fine to be hairy. It hasn't been like that for about a year.
Shin-chan, if you get into that kind of ruse, there are five people who'll think you're telling the truth, so I don't mind.
But it's a fan meeting, and only people who always support us are there.
I tried to do it on a dare, but I danced so much that I felt like a failure.
I was so worried that I would look like a failure. There are two more spacers.
I couldn't read your name in Korean, but it says "I love you".
Thank you.
How do you say it?What do you say?
Thank you very much.
I've been working hard to promote Kojima Hana-chan in the Amefura community.
I'd like to participate in the Amefura talk this time, but unfortunately I'm hearing impaired and can't understand what you guys are saying.
It's a pity that I can't understand what you guys are saying because of my hearing impairment, but it cheers me up to see you guys enjoying yourselves so much.
I would like to attend the live to see Kojimahana-chan and I will continue to support you.
Mushroom
I know I'm going to say I love this!
Thank you so much!
Kinokinokinoko
I got another stamp from a Korean speaker saying he's a big fan!
Thank you very much.
I love you
Can I get one more while I'm writing?
Yes.
It's from Mr. Fu.
This is my first spacha in my life!
I started at the TIG the other day.
I was able to listen to all the songs I wanted to hear at the live performance.
I also went to meet Ms. Ezuki Ichikawa at the benefit event.
Even though it was my first time, she welcomed me so warmly.
It was a very fun day!
I hope to visit Ammer next time.
It's going to be a hot day, so please rest well!
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
I remember you.
Definitely come see me!
No, thank you.
I know you think I'm watching you.
I'm often glad.
That's all. Grandma is for now.
Yes, ma'am.
Bye,
Are you still doing the hot pot?
No, I haven't done tanabe yet.No, I haven't done the daybed yet.
But I'm running out of time.
Let's just do the sun nabe.
That's why,
So that means..,
So the day when you have a whole day off for sightseeing is next week?
Next week.
A lot has happened.
I hope you'll all watch next week.
We have a lot of interesting things to talk about next week,
For now, let's talk about hot pot.
I'm sure you all want to hear about it, don't you?
Before we went to the restaurant, we were worried about whether we would be able to eat it.
We wondered if we could eat it.
And then it came out.
Then, there was a bright red liquid and a little whitish liquid.
Don't call it liquid.
You know what I mean.
Liquid.
This is the spicy one, and this is the normal Osaka flavor.
It looks so beautiful,
But I don't think I can eat the red one.
The red one looks spicy.
Yes, yes.
We said it would be nice if we could eat the regular one,
The meat arrived.
There's some kind of smoke coming out of it.
Of dry ice.A plate of expensive red meat came in a bar.
It was super delicious.
It was really delicious.
I was about 11 portions full.
I guess there are people who eat beef noodle.
Beef noodle and tapioca.
Souvenirs from the Isla Tower.
Sweet potato bowls.
Yes, I had a sweet potato bowl.
It was delicious.It was delicious.
The hot pot that arrived at the
It was so delicious.
It was super delicious.
I was surprised, wasn't I? It was that good.
The spicy soup was also delicious.
It was so delicious.
I could eat the sweets.
It was so spicy that I thought it was going to be a big hit.
If you like spicy food, it's definitely good.
It was super delicious.
It was terrible.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
It was spicy.
I can't do it.
I ate only the white ones.
It was great.
From the moment we walked in, there was a line for all-you-can-eat Haagen-Dazs ice cream.
There were about 12 kinds.
I decided to be the first to try it.
We all ate ice cream for now.
We ate ice cream, then hot pot, then ice cream, then hot pot, then ice cream, then hot pot.
To the staff who took us abroad so much.
It was the first time I saw someone taking Häagen-Dazs at the very beginning.
I have taken several staff pro idols.
I really recommend this place and I can take you there many times. Like, there's no group eating ice cream first.
I was like, "That's crazy.
There was a lot of meat and stuff.
About 5 pieces? About five plates of meat.
It was huge.
You have a picture, right?
I showed them.
As I thought, it was all meat. It was a lot of meat.
It came out.
Can you eat all of it? They asked us if we could finish it.
For us, this was really like an appetizer.For us, this was really, really like an appetizer.
From a feeling point of view.
Maybe from the staff's point of view over there, it's like, this is everything that's here.
That's a lot of food.
Even for a larger group of idols, it was said that it was too much to fill up.
I was told that maybe I would be so full that there would be enough left over for the rest of the meal.
Food. I want to be careful.
Food. Be careful.
Like, "Be really careful.
What do you think?
This is it.
That's great.
I always make mistakes.
Looks delicious.
Wait a minute.
I made a mistake with the spacing.
I always make mistakes.
It was so delicious.
It was so delicious, wasn't it?
Seafood.
They were pretty surprised.
And then we were like.
What does it mean that I can't eat this ice cream?
We were like, "Well, we're going to encourage them.
There were a dozen or so kinds of bald nuts.
But also meat. That's what it's all about.
Not like a towel, but like a serving dish.
You can scoop as much as you want. This is it, right?
I wonder how many of these plates there were. But there weren't enough at all.
There were about five or six plates. There weren't enough.
As you can imagine, it was huge. This is about the same size, right? The plates.
The plate of meat is this big.
It's pretty much this big. Really this big.
I counted it with one hand and put it in like this, so it was pretty much the same size.
But I didn't have enough, so I added more.
We had beer, too, right?
I added more and thought, "I can eat as many plates as I want.I added a few more and decided how many plates I could handle.
But I'll leave that up to you guys, since flowers have a bug in their values.
So, I made it about 6, right?
Two, two, four, six, I don't know.
I don't know. Anyway, I'll take one for now.
But I think it should be 6 or so.
I made it 4 or 6, because there were two.
There were two of them, so I had one more, and then I ate that, and then there was one more rack of meat.
The staff found it.
You mean you won't involve me?
No, just Kama-chan. He found it.
Like the young kids wouldn't be able to taste the meat. The adults.
They wanted to give them the cheap stuff.
It's for pawn.
But we came here as if we were the pawns,
We also wanted to eat the expensive ones even if we couldn't taste them,
If you can't taste it, does that mean you can eat the expensive food?
Just in case, you might be able to tell.
It looks delicious. You said you wanted to eat it.
But you ordered two plates.
You asked for another one for us.
No, no, no.
You were going to eat both plates, weren't you?
That's not true.
I wasn't going to give them to you at all.
But then, you know, people are kind, so you gave them to us. They gave it to us.
We ate it and said it was really delicious.
But you didn't have much because it was expensive.
The adults had to eat one more piece of seafood or something.
We were trying to put in the good stuff after the meat with the dry ice was gone.
Then they started saying, "You can have this one, too.
There's still some left over here.
Do you want to put the next one in soon?
We were trying to fill our stomachs with that one.
We were the ones who were eating the high-end meat.
We said, "We'll eat the high-end meat, too, when we're full.
No, no, no. There is plenty of it over there.No, no, no. We have a lot over there.
Only meat soup stock.
Only premium meat soup stock.
But the flowers, what is that?
But, our Mr. Kojima is really good.
I've never seen an MC with his arms folded like this.
He was doing his best.
And then there was our Mr. Kojima.
He was so kind as to take the adult team's high-end meat and put it into our pot.
I've got it.
Isn't it pretty cool? The size.
He was really angry. He was really mad.
He really was.
It was delicious.
It was super delicious.
Normally, it's this hot pot, but the staff member who took me there said, "I've never seen a staple idol who ate so much.
The staff member who took me there said, "I've never seen a staple idol who ate so much food.
He said he took a maximum of nine people with him.
There were about three groups.
More than nine.
There were 10 or so people in the group, but four of them insisted they were eating more than that.
I said, "Of course not.
It's definitely not like that.
They had already eaten, so they could have eaten more.
That was about half.
There was no way they were number one.
But the staff always said that they didn't believe that I, an idol, ate a lot or that I was a glutton.
But when I saw Amehura, I believed him.
From now on, when you see idols like that, just snicker at them.
Amehura is Amehura!
I'm going to go up.
I know the real thing," he said.
I told him to go out and have a beer with number 9.
First, fill up on tapioca, Starbucks, sweet potato balls, and beef.
I probably shouldn't have taken advantage of the upscale restaurant in Amefula.
But the rice was all-you-can-eat.
Like all you can take.
I was eating the rice as I ate it too,We were eating rice as we went along,
At the end of the meal, we decided that we wanted to use the soup to make a rice porridge,
When we decided to do it at the very last minute, the staff was so excited that they brought a number of groups to the party,
I brought a number of groups with me, but I had never seen such a group doing such a thing.
I've never seen a group do that before. I've never seen a group do that before.
Closing is a matter of course.
It's a normal thing.
And since all the soup is also used as rice porridge, it runs out.
This is the first time I've ever seen this place cracking up.
I saw it for the first time, and so did the local staff there,
Or there was no more rice in the rice cooker at that time.
It was right before closing time, so there was no more rice in the rice cooker,
They didn't cook any more rice.
I went and asked if there was any more rice in the rice cooker. I asked her if they had any more,
They said, "No, we don't have any more.
But after that, they brought me a bowlful, saying, "Wait a minute.
But it was only one bowl of ameflower. Only one person could eat it.
This is not enough.
I want to eat it with four people.
We wanted two more bowls.
I confirmed it, but I had beef noodle.
We ate the rice vermicelli.
So, why did I ask the woman?
I said, "Sory, rice, plus two,
Rice?  Rice?
She said, "Oh my god," and walked away,
She looked really confused.
He looked really annoyed.
If you go back and have a little time,
I got two more drinks than the one I had just had.
I'm sure the employee was an idiot.
I'm sure they are.
That's right.
It's Dekin.
But when I said "thank you very much" to many people,
They were like, "Wow, you did a great job.
You did a great job, eating all the leftovers.
I ate all of it.I ate all the leftovers.
It was delicious.
Then, I took a picture of my stomach afterwards.
Your own?
By all means.
I would love to have you ride with me.
These two guys were taking pictures, too.
I was taking shots of their bellies.
They are both pregnant.
It was that day, wasn't it?
I'm already in the elevator.
It's really bad.
The elevator was mirrored.
And Aiara and I were riding alone,
Aiara raised the elevator quite a bit, and we were taking pictures of the mirror,
And we were taking pictures of the mirrors,
I thought there must be some kind of surveillance camera, and I looked at it and saw that there was one.
It was definitely a bad idea.
I was disgusted.
This time, I only wanted to eat it.
It was a commemorative event.
That's right.
What do you mean by "memorable belly"?
I've never seen anything like it.
I wanted to talk about who was paired with who at the hotel.
Yes, we would have.
Next time?
Next time we will talk about who was paired with who in the hotel.
There are quite a few different stories.
It's all intertwined.
This installment will be broadcast over the next seven weeks or so.
Malaysia is coming.
You think it will end in Malaysia?
We're going to finish it next week.
Oh no.
Malaysia is coming.I'm coming to Malaysia.
Next week we'll talk about that and two other things that happened when I was already off in Malaysia.
Where did you go?
Oh no. I forgot.
I don't know what to do.
But TIFF was really hot, and I was able to meet up with a lot of my idols,
It was really great.
I lost the tambourine championship by one decibel.
Both Sky Stage and Heat Stage were a lot of fun.
Thanks for your hard work.
It was a really great stage.
I got along well with the cell phone people too.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
Please come back next year.
You had more content.
We talked a lot about TIFF.
I think TIFF and Taiwan won't be invited.
I talked about Taiwan and TIFF this time,
Can I close now?
That was amazing. We've had so many episodes that something has happened to us.
Yes, it is.
We'll be talking more and more about Taiwan over the next week.
How do you say it?
Yo!
Repeat three times!
LOL!
Nice!
That's what I'm talking about!
Very funny!
Oh my god!
The seniors are awesome!
It's so frustrating that we couldn't get into it!
We didn't know how to get in!
I'll try again next week!
Thank you very much!
Okay, I'll leave you with this.Okay, well, last but not least.
I would like to go to the Announcements section!
There are more announcements to come!
I've got a lot more, so let's get to it!
Let's start with me!
Okay, I'll go first! Tomorrow, August 4th
I will be appearing on Shake Up Up!
Yay!
This time, this time.
The limited special edition times are
Yuzuki Ichikawa
Yuzu Ichikawa vacation?
Yuzu Ichikawa's off.
Ah!
Ichikawa Summer Vacation Homework
It's a calligraphy homework, so I wrote four letters of my choice
With a calligraphy pen?
With a brush.
You can write them with a brush.
I hate calligraphy.
That's why I'm not very good.
I'm not very good, but I can write four letters.
The one you want.
Can you write "B-hump"?
B-fun is fine, whatever.
I'll write four letters.
But I'm not good at it. I'm always...
Um...
Oh, my...
After spring break, my friend wrote calligraphy.
I don't want it.
I'll take the one that was a little bad.
It's not as good as the one I got from my friend.
But if you still like it
I will write it. But I will put love into it.
If you like
Please come. AndPlease come. And
August 14
Next Monday.
Sheikh Alop's special program
for a special summer program special.
I've been invited to be a part of it.
That means...
Ditch the ameshave
Ditched the ameshave
I got the experience of Amershabe
we could step up to the next place.
He left us.
I knew this Ameshave was the one
to step up to the next place.
It's also a practice for the next step up.
I mean, we've flown the coop.
Only one of us
I can fly away on my own
I could flap my wings
It means I've got wings
I'd like to be allowed to do my best
I'm just going to throw this week's story out there.
You're going that way, aren't you?
You're the most half-assed woman I've ever met.
That sucks.
Diet sucks.
I'm really in the middle of a lot of people.
Tickets are sold out.
But you can still watch the streaming video.
I'd be very happy if you could watch it.
And this week is just around the corner!
On Saturday, August 12th
I will be performing at the Summer Station Music Live
I will be performing at the Summer Station Music Live!
This is a concert with Philosophy of Dance
and Philosophy Dance.
at 11:30am.The show will start at 11:30am!
Tickets are now on sale to the general public!
We are really looking forward to it, so
Oh, man.
The other day at T-HU.
I met with Mr. Philosophy of Dance.
I'm so excited.
I can't believe we're going to be in Summer Station Music.
I'm so excited to be a part of Summer Station.
Last year you said you'd love to be a part of Summer Station.
That's what you said.
Whenever you had a job around here...
"Wow, we're going to be on the Summer Station stage.
We were talking about it.
I'm so excited that we're going to be able to do it this year.
I'm a little worried about the rain.
There's a roof over our heads.
Hilderleigh on the side, right?
Yes!
We'll do a little bit of that for the guests.
That's good.
But the footing will be bad, so if you're coming by plane or bullet train, please be careful.
Let's have fun together!
Let's feel the summer!
And the next day, August 13th, is Namie's annual convention.
Tickets are now available.
Tickets are still available. That's what I'm talking about.
It's going to be hot!
We'll be playing in the water.
Summer fun?
Can I say we're gonna play in the water?
We are!
I'm announcing it.
It's like a boo-boo.
What?
They said there's more than twice as much water as last year.
Are you ready to get soaked? Gentlemen.Are you ready to get soaked? Gentlemen.
But there's a Muji nearby, so if anything goes wrong, I'm sure we'll be fine.
As for tickets, the trucks are already on their way.
But, um...
We'll even have a big pillow at the plaza.
It's going to be held at Namie Roadside Station.
So if you're driving in Namie Town...
You might be able to see it.
It's okay if you don't want to be seen at all.
You'd better dress for the wet.
That's right.
Can we bring a change of clothes?
I'd better bring some heat, too.
I'm going to do it with my face, so please be careful.
Please.
Yes, this is Nikonny.
We'll be broadcasting live on Nico Nico Knee.
I'll be appearing on Jinchami Publications.
I'm so excited!
What's it going to be like?
It's going to be amazing!
Oh my god! I only have one more to go, so I might run out already!
Bye bye everyone!
Why is there always no charge?
I had like 50 bottles left and now I'm out.
But I'm really looking forward to meeting you all.
And I'm really looking forward to meeting Mr. Tanaka, who is a collector of his own stuff.
I'm really looking forward to meeting you.
It's going to be a lot of fun, so please come and watch!
Jinnah, is that you?
I'm so happy!
It looks so Egyptian!
I love Yoochamichan!
I've been watching you since the pop tease days.
I hope you remember me because I did it today at the chorus battle.
And here she is on August 23rd.
100% chance of perfume from Cookpad Live!
There will be a Happy Amen Cafe!There will be a Happy Amen Cafe!
Yuzu and Aira will be performing!
Anyone can watch it on the app or something.
Please watch their cooking!
Thank you very much!
Aira Hana was great the other day!
Moe Kahana was great too!
Thank you very much!
I'm sorry, everyone.
Please take a break.
And we will be at Jam again this year!
Ameflas will be performing on August 26th!
Tickets are on sale now.
It's a side show.
I'm sure you're all familiar with it.
Let's have fun together!
Thank you very much!
And I'm going to Malaysia!
Less than two weeks away!
Oh no!
But the other night at 3:00...
It ended yesterday.
I was doing the 3:00.
I'm sorry, but we're closed.
If you want to go with me...
Take care and go together.
I got a DM saying he decided to go to Malaysia.
We're coming together.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad I did it at 3:00.
It's not easy to get people to come to Malaysia, isn't it?
I mean, Malaysia is a 7-hour flight.
We just had Taiwan the other day.
I didn't know if there was even one person who would come to Malaysia.
I was afraid that only one person would come.
I thought it would be better if only one person came to Malaysia.
That's really true.
Thank you very much.I appreciate it.
First time in Malaysia.
First time in Malaysia
Let's have fun!
And the Staff Ride Festival will be held
This time it's a harvest festival of new songs in autumn.
You might be able to hear a lot of new songs and more!
Ticket details will be announced later!
Sunday, October 29th.
Please come everyone!
Please do.
This is the last one.
Yes, and the second part of the Bang Woo Sai event we held on July 9 will be streamed on U-NEXT on August 10, starting at 20:00.
It will be available in a little while.
Like 3 days later.
Members will be able to watch it without additional charge.
So, we hope you'll watch it, too.
We saw it, didn't we? We did see it.
We received a canned packet distributed by U-NEXT.
I saw it, and the camera work was really cool.
It was packed with a lot of goodness that was different from what you see at a live concert.
Please take a look if you like.
Please watch it.
And the goods for the Bang Woo Sai.
They will be on sale from 6:00 p.m. on Tuesday, August 8.
This is a T-shirt, a 4-cut key chain, a penlight, and a penlight sheet,
We will be selling the 90-season fresh photo for the first time.
Some of them are 90 yen.
We have a few more for 100 yen.
What would you like to spend 100 yen for? Bikinis?
Please come in.
Go ahead.
We're just in costumes.
We are costumes.
We are new costumes.
New costumes.
I want to wear a new costume, too.
She wants to wear a bikini.They want bikinis.
It's OK.
We are styling.
Please.
I don't care about those things.
Goods will be sold.
We'll start selling them here on the day of Bang Woo Sai because they were sold out or something,
Please buy them if you want.
What? Is that what this is about?
I thought something was a little strange.
Let me see.
I thought it was white.
I'm reading it while looking at it.
I thought there was something there.
It's being projected.
I wondered why I didn't do that.
There was no paper.
All I had was a pamphlet.
There was a copy on the back of the paper.
He wrote everything on the back. The staff wrote everything on the back.
I thought there was something there.
I thought the way they put it on was really white.
White.
It's just stupid.
Ameharashi's 5th Anniversary Live will be held at Shinagawa Stellar Ball on Friday, December 22nd.
It will be held at Shinagawa Stellar Ball on Friday, December 22nd.
The official temporary selection is until 23:59 on August 14.
I hope everyone will come so that we don't forget you, but we definitely want you to soul out,
Bayou-san was also able to soul out, so we would like to take another step forward with consecutive soul-outs, so please give us your support.
I really appreciate your support.
I am sure it will be a great concert.
Not for sure. Definitely.
I'm really fired up about it.
I'm having too much fun.
I'm having too much fun, too much fun,
I'm worried that everyone will be all "ah-ha!" on that day.
I'm worried that everyone will be in shape on that day.What if I get it all set up?
What if I get too organized and can't make it home from the venue?
Then let's all stay the night together.
There is a hotel, isn't there?
That's nice. Does that mean it's effective?
Of course. Because even after the show, we always look like that.
It's like, "Oh, my God, I'm so happy.
After the show, everyone is like, "It's over..." and they take a lot of pictures of the metal ring.
They bring all the souvenirs.
They all bring a big bag like this.
After the bio-sci show the other day, the staff had to put everything in four big paper bags,
It was pretty heavy.
It was very heavy.
It was hard work, but the food was delicious.
Thank you very much.
I will do my best. I hope you all grow a lot of friends.
Please do.
Yes, please. So I would like to go to this corner for the last time.
Thank you for waiting.
Hello, Swee.
Is it Swi today?
No, he is not. Today's Mr. Swi is wearing a hoodie and a hat,
He is Swee-kun who played Mr. Parker Jr.
Ayanan's Dad's Voice
Is he wearing a watermelon hat? Watermelon.
It's cute.
Flowers are strawberries.
The flowers are strawberries and the watermelon is a watermelon.
Cute.
Thank you very much.
How's it feel to move of your own volition?
Hana-dad was funny, wasn't he?
Since when do you move of your own volition?
Most of the time, I'm controlled by others.
You're becoming this week's HanaDada.
No, no, no, no.No, no, no, no.
Just be this week's flower daddy. Oh, no.
Oh no.
Give me a break.
I think Hana Dad's in a good mood.
My corner?
Stop it.
Keep doing my corner.
I sent you my video today, so get it out.
You're not that kind of a character.
You always say that.
I never said that.
I want to be in it, too.
Anytime.
We're here for you, flower daddy.
Please come back to the archive.
It's okay.
If you want to see it, please go up the archive 100th anniversary of the archive.
It's OK.
Please take a look.
Hana Papa was cool.
I want to delete the archive.
That's the one that got the most entries.
Han-chan was really pissed off.
Really.
My parents are going to be on the show.
How do you think he felt?
Was that a surprise?
Aya and her friends came beforehand.
I didn't know about the flowers.
I really thought I was going to break down crying.
It was a mess.
It really was.
Yes, we are always ready for you.
It was Suikun again this week.
Yes, this is Toyooki.
It's time to say goodbye.
I wish everyone a good week at the end,I hope that everyone will do their best for the week at the end,
I would like to leave you with a corner of Moe Kakara, Ganbaru Spell, and Moe Moe Magic.
Yes, please come in.
Please come on in.
Another week, another dodger AC lifer!
Am I right?
Yes, but this week too.
Make some noise.
Yes, I know.
Darger AC Lifers.
It's summer vacation, so the difference is that I'm going to tell you to make some noise in Taiwanese.
I think it's hard because it's summer vacation and usually everyone is at work,
I know students are also busy with school,
But at least enjoy the summer vacation mood,
We have started fireworks, food stalls, and so on,
So let's make a lot of noise and blow stuff up,
We can have a lot of fun and enjoy the summer with them,
Let's have fun with them.
If that's the case, it's too long.
That's right.
It's a little too long.
The supplement.
That's what it means.
That's right.